Hi guys, my name is Nitesh and welcome
to my YouTube channel.  In this video also we will
continue our fast API playlist.
Now what are we going to do in this video
?  Before we dive into this,
let's take a quick recap of
what we did in the last video.  So if you remember,
if you have watched the previous video,
there we had built a machine learning model
on the problem of insurance
premium prediction.  Basically what we were doing was
we took a data set where
we had users' data.  Ok?
About their lifestyle, about their personal
information and on that basis we were
trying to predict whether the
insurance premium of that particular customer will be
high or medium
or low.  Ok?  So to predict this
we built a Random Forest machine
learning model and we
exported that model.  Ok?  And
then what did we do?  An API was built on top of this model
using Fast API.
So basically we
created an end point by using a slash predictor.  Where if you
send information of a new user, this end
point will tell us
what will be the insurance premium of that particular new user.
Ok?  So we built this API and
then in the last I also showed you a
front end created with the help
of
Streamlet where we were hitting this API
and sending the user's data there
and in return we were seeing the response.
We did this in the last video.
Ok?  So, now going forward there are
three more things I have to do in this playlist.
This API that we have created, we
first have to improve it a little bit.  Right?
When you're in the industry, when you work in a company
and you make APIs, they're a little bit
more production grade.  Those are a little
better.  The API we just
created is a little basic.  So
what are we going to do in today's video?  We
will improve this API.  Ok?  Once we
improve this API, then
in the next video we will Dockerize this whole API
application with the help
of Dockers.  And in the last video of the
playlist, we will deploy and run that dockerized application
on AWS.
Ok?  So, these are our three tasks.
Going forward in the next three videos.
But whatever it is, our task in today's video is
that we will improve a little bit the API that we built in the last video.
Ok?  So what
are the improvements?  I have written it here.
We will do almost at different improvements
and by the end of the video you will
realize that you have actually improved the API that you
created in the last video.
Ok?  So this
is a very interesting video and please
watch it till the end.  Because in the next two videos
we will deploy this improved API.
Ok?  So with that let's start the
video.  Before making improvements to the API,
we first run and test our API.
Ok?  So here is our
project folder.  Here we have this app.   We
created our API inside Py.  So let's
run it once and try it out to see if
things are working properly or
not.  So we ran the uvicon command
and our API started.  So
we're going to go over to Slash Docs.  So here
is our API.  Let's try it once.
It's a good idea.  Whenever you are
resuming a project, you
should try running the project once.  So
try it out.  Age 35 Weight 90 Height
1.72 Income 15 LPA Smoker Lets
Live in True City Gurgaon and Occupation Retired.
Execute and you can see we are
getting the response predicted category is
high.  Ok?  So this means that right now our
project and our API are
working properly.  Ok?  Now from here we will
start our improvements.
So the first improvement that I have planned is that
how it is now,
that in the project where our API is located, in the
folder where it is located, we have done a
lot of other work there too.  Ok?  So earlier
I taught you the fundamentals of Fast API,
so its code is also written here.  The
Jupyter Notebook code for the machine learning model we built is also
written here.  This is some JSON file also
lying here.  So basically the problem is
that we have
not developed our API independently.  We have
just kept it like this in some other folder
with some other things.  Ok?  This is
not a good idea.  When you create a Docker container for
your API, you would like
your API to
exist independently in a folder.  Meaning it
should have its own project folder.  Ok?
So the first thing that we do is that we will
create a separate folder for our API.  Ok
?  And in that only we will do all the work related to our API.
Ok?  So what I will do
is first of all I will create a new
folder.  Ok?  So here I am
creating a new folder.  Let's name the folder
An Insurance Premium
Prediction.  Ok?  And what do we have to do inside this folder
?  We have to place
our app.  You have to paste the py file.
And secondly, we also have to bring this model
pkl file which is our serialized machine
learning model.
Because with its help we will make predictions.
So what I will do is that here
I have model dot PKL.  I am copying it here
and
creating a new folder here by opening the folder containing Insurance Premium Prediction.
And I am naming this folder
models.  Ok?  So anything related to ML model,
we are putting it inside this folder.  So
we put our model.pk file here.  The
second thing that we have to do is that
we have to create our app.py file here.
Ok?  So let's do one thing for him.
First of all, we open this new folder
inside VS Code.  Ok
?  And we will create this app inside VS code itself.
Now we need one more thing to
run this whole thing and that is that
when we were working here
in the old folder, we had
created a virtual environment here.  You can say 'see
my ENV' and inside this virtual
environment we
installed all our libraries.  So
we will need exactly the same set of
libraries in our new folder
as well.  So what we can do is rather than
reinstalling all the libraries.  What we
can do is that we create a requirements.xt
file.  Ok?  So
basically you have to write this command pip freeze
greater than requirements.xt.  As soon as
you run this command you will get a file.
Here is that file.  The command has
not yet been completed.  But it's
done now.  Look here is the
list of all the libraries that we have
used so far in our project.  Ok
?  You can see here you will see Cost API.
Here's the fast API
Pydentik will show you.  You will
see the request because we used the requests library while building the front end.
PsychLearn will appear.  Starlet
Streamlet It's all visible.  So
we need this file also.  So let's do one thing.
This is our old folder.  And here is the
app.py in it and here is the
requirements.txt.  We
need both these files inside our insurance premium
folder.  Ok?  So, this is what we got here.
Now let's do one thing.  Let's open this folder
inside VS Code.  Open
folder.  Here is this folder.  So, you can see this is
our
app.py.  This Is Our Requirements.xt.
Ok?  Now from this I will remove some things
which are not required.  And the
reason for deleting it is that I can keep it as well.  But
what will go wrong if we keep this is that in the next video,
when we will Dockerize our application using Docker,
then the size of the Docker image becomes
bigger.  So
I am removing those unnecessary libraries.
Like I'm not going to use streamlet.
Similarly I would not be using
requests.  So I will simply remove these two libraries.
And apart from this,
if there is anything which is not needed then we
can remove it.  I'll have to
pause the video and check it once.  The butt is fine after that.
For now, we have removed these two libraries.  Now
here is our app.py, we will have to make a small change in it.
A, the location of this model PKL has
changed a bit.  Now it
is inside the models folder.  Ok?  So
here we will write model sash model PKL and
apart from this everything else will remain exactly the same according to me.
Ok?  So now let's do one thing.
From inside this new folder we can
run our project and see.  So we are
creating a new terminal.  Here
we will first create a new virtual environment.
Python - MV env my
environment.  The virtual environment has been created.
We will activate it once.
So we will write my
env
scripts activate.  Ok?  It has been activated.
Now what we will do here is that
we will install all the libraries that are in the requirements.  So we will write
pip
install --requirements.txt
Now all the libraries which are
required to run this project
like API pidtik, all of them are getting installed.
So this is the advantage of
bringing Requirements.xt into the picture.
If we didn't bring requirements.php, we would have to
manually remember
which libraries we have installed there.
Ok?  So he is fulfilling the requirements.
Let's wait until all these
libraries are installed.  And
guys we installed all the libraries.
Ok?  Now the next
step is that we will try running our application once.
So to run it we have to
run the uvicon command.  That is
uvicon app click on app minus reload and
you can see our app is running.  We have to go to
Dox API Pay and you can see our
API is loading.  Let's try it once.
Try it out.  Age is 31 Weight is
81 Height is
1.7 Income is 10 LPA Smoking is true
City is Mumbai Occupation is Retired
Apart from retired I guess there were other things too
Private Job Business Owner Right now since I ca
n't remember what was there so let's
keep Retired and execute it
and you can see the predict category is
low.  Ok?  So this API is now working
fine.  But the good thing is that now we have
created a dedicated project folder of our own and we are doing
all the development inside that.  So this was the
first improvement we
wanted to make.  And we are done with this one.  Now
I will tell you what the next improvement we need to make is.  So there is
a problem with our current API.   The
problem is that when you are setting this city field,
you have to
write the name of the city in title case.  Meaning,
whoever will be our API client, he has to
write the name of the city in title case.  Title
case means your first letter should be
in capital and everything else should be
in small.  So as it
is written Mumbai here then it is correct.  But if you
make it small M Mumbai then
what will be the problem that it will not happen that any error will come.
But
we will treat Mumbai as a tier three city.  Look
here, if you go into your code, you will
see that we have defined our tier
one cities in this way.  This is how
we have defined our tier two cities.
Now if you send small M in M ​​here
then what will happen is that this Mumbai will
not match and you will consider Mumbai as a tier three
city.  So basically what do we
have to do?  Here we will
have to add a field validator in our Pydantic model
with the help of which we will convert city into title case.
If it is not in title case
then it will come in title case.  Ok?  So
I have already written its code.  Let me
show you quickly.  Here is its
simple code.  Let me just paste this
in here and then let me discuss
what we are doing.  So I
just went here next to our pydantic model and
I pasted this code here.   There is a
slight indentation issue and
we have not imported the field validator
from Pydantic, so we will import it.
Field Validator Now look here the
code is very simple.  As soon as we get the city,
we are stripping it from our clients.
Which basically means that if there is
any extra white space before or after the city name,
we are removing it
and then the city name that is coming is being
converted into title case and
returning it.  So what
happens now?  After adding this code,
you can send it by writing Mumbai like this or
send it by writing it in title case.  You
will get the same output.  We will treat Mumbai like a tier one city.
Look, the value has
started coming back.  What was happening earlier was that if it was
small m then the value was coming low and if it was
capital m then a different value was coming.
Ok?  So what did we do to get this consistency
?  Added a field validator.
Now our cities will be treated properly.
Ok?  So this was our second improvement
which we just did.  The next problem we have
with our API is that our
API does not have a home endpoint.   What
I mean by that is if you ever
load our API and you hit its home
URL.  Basically slash URL so
you will not see anything here.
Ok?  This is the problem.  So, ideally
what should happen is that there should be a message on your home URL
saying that
your company's API is hosted here.  Ok?
So, what we can do is that we come here
in our code and
we can add an end point.  app.get.
And here we are adding a function by calling home.
And in this function we are simply
returning a dictionary which
contains the
message and here it is written Insurance
Premium
Prediction API.  Ok?  Now what will happen is
that if someone hits our home URL
then he will see this message.  Ok?  So at
least through this we understand that
our API is working properly.
Ok?  So this is one thing we had to add.
Along with this we should add one more thing.
So basically we
should add another end point here.  So what happens is that
when you go to host your API
on a cloud platform like AWS and there if you
use any service like Kubernetes or Elastic Load Balancer
of AWS, then they force you to
add a health check endpoint to your API.
What is this health check end point?  This
helps AWS know
that your API is live and
working properly.  So this is also recommended.  So
what should we do?  We will define another end point by
saying health.  And inside this
we will create a function called health check.
And it will simply return two or three things to you.
First it will tell you the status
of the API.  We will write OK here.  And
apart from this you can tell many more things here.
Like when was the last time your API was
updated.  Apart from this, you
can also mention here that you have loaded your ML model.
If you are connecting to a database then
you can mention here that
you have connected to the database.  Ok
?  Let's do one thing for now.  Just
put the status as OK and see.  Ok?  So if I
go back and put slash health here and hit
enter then I should be getting status
okay.  So this is my health check API.
Ok?  Now I know you might be thinking that
both these things seem redundant.
If home is an end point, then
why are we keeping this health end point?  The reason for this is
that this first
home endpoint that we have defined is human readable.
We made it for humans.  Anyone
hitting our URL can see
that the API is working correctly.
Wear edge, this second one that we have made is
machine readable.  We created this because
some of the services of AWS like
Kubernetes or Elastic Load
Balancer will go and
hit this endpoint and if they
see the status as OK here, only then
your API will be deployed properly on those
platforms.  So the reason for adding this is
simply that we have to deploy it to our
endpoints, our API on the cloud services
and there they will
force us to do this.  Ok?  So I hope
you are understanding this thing.  Ok?  There's one
more thing I'd like to mention here.
I have written it here also.  So we have added these two new
end points.  One more thing
I would like to do is we
also expose a model version in our health check API.
It's a good practice.  Ok
?  Ok.  So basically what I want is that
somehow after loading the model here, we can
create a variable here by saying model version and let's say the
model version is 1.0.0
okay?  I have done this manually at the moment.   I have
created my own version number.  But
generally the model version that comes here
comes from a software like ML Flow.
Ok?  The Model Registry in ML Flow is
a component of Bol.  The model registry
automatically keeps track of
which version of a model you currently have.  Ok?
So, we have created this manually for now.  But
in an ideal scenario you will extract this from ML flow.
So for now let's assume
our model version is 1.0.0.  So what I would
like to do is that I would
also pass this information to my health check API.
Version Model Version.  Ok?  So what will
happen now is that if someone goes to our Health Check API
then he will see both these things
that the status is OK.  It means our API is
running and the version is this.  So he will keep
getting the version information also.  Ok?  And as
I said, you can add other things here also.  The
model has been loaded.  You
can tell me like this.  Here you can add model
loaded.  And here I can write model
is true.  Ok?  Above we have loaded the model
here.  If this model is loaded here.
model is If model is not none then true will
come.  If the model is a nun then it will fall.  Let's
try it once.
Look the model is showing loaded true.  Meaning the
model powering this API has been loaded.
This is the version of that model.  The status
is OK.  Meaning the API is live.  Ok?
Again, I am explaining this to you again and again that
we have done this to make
our API machine readable.  Otherwise there is no need for this.
We could have managed our work from here also.
Ok?  So this is something you have to do
when you're building an industry grade API.
So we completed this part also.  The
next improvement is that we will
make our code a little cleaner.
Making it clean means that now if you
go to your appy file then you will notice
that we have written all the code here
in this single file.  Our
pydantic model is inside this file.
This is where we are loading our ML model.   We are getting
the predictions done right here.  And
apart from this, all the code of Fast API is also here.
This is not a good strategy.  Ideally there
should be a separation of concerns.  This means
that the fast API file
should contain only routing code.  The pydantic
model should be in a separate file.  The code for
loading the ML model and making predictions
should be in a separate file.  So
what will we do now?  We will implement separation of concerns.
So first of all what I will
do is that the Pydantic model that we have
created, this big Pydantic model that
we have created, we will put it in a different
file and we will load that file
here.  Ok?  So what I will do
is first of all I will create a
new folder and I am calling this
schema.  Ok?  And inside this schema I am
creating a new file by the name of
user input dot py.  Ok?  And now what
I will do is that whatever is my code of
Pydantic model, I will cut that entire code.
This much I will cut and I will
paste it in user input.  There are some
errors coming here and mostly the errors are because
we have kept the import of pydantic here.
So I'm going to cut this as well
and paste it here.  After saving,
many errors were removed.  There might still be some errors
I guess.  And those errors are that
he is not getting tier one cities and tier two cities.
So what I will do is that
I will pick up these two components from our original file
and paste them here.
Ok?  Now our user input py is
working correctly.  Now what we need to do is
here you will notice that now the user
input is not being identified.  So to
identify it, we will write
from schema dot user input we will
import User Input class.
We have created the whole class here.  But we are loading it here
and using it.  No
error is coming.  Let's do one thing.  Let us
cross check once whether our API is
working properly or not.  So we
went to the docks.  You Can See Home looks different.
Health looks different.  The prediction
is here.  Simply go for a try out.
Age
Weight 91 Height 1.5 10
LPA City Is Mumbai Retired
Executor And You Can See 200 Predicted
Category Medium is coming.  So that means
even after all the refactoring we just did, our API is still working properly.
Ok?  So this is the first improvement
we planned is that we
removed the pydantic model.  Next what happens is that
here if you go to the pedantic model,
here we have defined tier one cities and tier two
cities by making a big list like this.
Ideally you
should do this also in a separate file.  So what we can do is
we can create one more folder.  Let's
call it config and inside config let's
create a file city tear dot py and what
we will do is nothing much.  We will
cut this entire code and paste it here.
Ok?  And here we will simply
write from config dot city tier
import tier one cities tier two cities.  Ok
?  So now what, our pedantic model is also
completely clean.  Only the
code of the pydantic model is written here.  The
name of the cities is written here and the
code of the latest API plus machine learning is written here.
Now what will we do next?  We will also separate the
machine learning code from our API code.
Now to
separate the machine learning code,
first thing we will do is go to our model
folder where our ML
model is currently stored.  Here we will create a new file
called predict.py and
we will write all the code for prediction here.
So first of all we will
write the code to load the model here.  So I will
cut this much code.  We will also write a version of the infact model
inside our predict.py.
Ok?  For this we will have to
import pickles and tomatoes.
So we put these imports here.
And next what we'll do is
create a function in this file
predict.py.  Let's call it
predict output.
Ok?  The predict output will get
a user input dictionary to do its job.  You will
get the user input dictionary and
what do you have to do here?  The first thing to do is to
convert this dictionary into a data frame.
So we'll write pd dot data frame
user input and we'll put it into a variable by calling it input df.
What will we do after that?  The code that we have
written here, we will put this exact code here.
Ok?  As soon as we
got the input df, we
called Model.Predict.  After turning around we got our output.
And this is the output we are returning.
Ok?  Let's save this file and let's
go here once again and we will make some changes.
So the first change is that now we do
n't need to convert it into a data frame here.  We simply need a dictionary
and we can call it user underscore
input here.  Then what will we do?
We're not going to call model dot predict.
We'll just call
predictOutput whatever the name of this function is.  We will
call predictOutput and
from here we will send the user input.  This will
invert the predict output and give us our
output.  That will be our prediction.
Ok?  Just what do we have to do now?  This
predict output function needs to be imported.
So what will we do for that?  We
will write this code.  from model dot predict
import predict output .
Ok?  So we have refactored the code.   There
is one more problem.  A here it is saying that the
model is not true.  So if you want, you
can import the model from here and at the same time
you can also import the model version
from this file.  Here you have the
model loaded and here you have the
model version also.  So we imported both these things.
Now there
is no error anywhere.  And what is a good thing?  Now,
in the code of our Fast API, you will
not see any machine learning code anywhere.
Ok?  Neither are we loading the model here nor are we making
it make predictions.
We are now doing all this work
in predict.py.  Again as I said,
separation of concerns.  Let's run this code once and
see.  Because we have made major changes.
It's always a good idea to
try out
your API after major refactoring to see if it is working properly.
Age 31 91
1.72 Income 10 LPA string will be replaced by
Mumbai.  Occupation retired
execute and there is some error.  Let me check
what error is this?  See, the error is that
when we created the data frame here in predict.py,
we did not tell it
how many days we need in our data frame.
So what do you have to do?
While passing this dictionary, it has to be sent in a list.
Now if you go back and
execute again you will see that your
API is working.  Ok?  So this
was a small error.  But after resolving this, the
benefit we get now is that our
API is very properly refactored.  There is
separation of concerns and
our API has become very clean.  Ok?  Let's make one more small
change.  Ah, we have done all this.  We will keep
updating here once in a while.
We took apart the city tier.
Separated out the ML logic.  Let's
add one more trycat statement.  So here you will
see that we are making a prediction and
then returning the result.  But this
prediction is dependent on the working of an external file.
So
anytime in such scenario you should write try catch.
Try Accept in Python.  So you will
try to write it.  And you will do these two things inside the try.
And here you will write
accept exception as e.  And here you will
return a JSON response whose
status code will be 500 Internal Server Error and
your content here will be the
string of e.  Ok?  Whatever
error there is, we will print it.  So
we have added a try accept block
so that if some code breaks here,
we can handle it gracefully.  Ok
?  So, we have completed this one thing also.   The
next improvement is guys, we
want to make the output of our API a little more rich.  Rich means we
want to provide a little more information.
What is happening currently is that our
API is simply returning
whether the insurance premium of our customer, the user, will be
high, medium
or low.  Right?  If you go and
see the output you would see this is what we are
getting.  But what if I want to
show some more things here.  Like I
also want to show
what is the confidence score of being high?  Meaning,
what does our model think?  What is the percentage chance of it
being high?  We want to tell this.
Let's say it's 73.  So we would like to not only
tell that the output of the model is high
but at the same time we would also like to give this confidence score.
Infact not only that, we would
also like to tell you that if the model thought 73 was high
then what was the medium?  Suppose 17 so
how much did it cost
? 10 So we want to show this whole thing to the user.
Ok?  And the best
part is that you can do this easily.
Because you have used Random Forest model
which not only gives prediction but
also gives you confidence score.  Ok
?  So there is nothing special to do.  We have to
go to our predict.py function and change this
simple code that we have written.
Ok?  Our code will now
look like this.  First of all,
we will write this one thing outside this function and here
user input will come in place of data.
Once I write the code correctly.  Then I will
explain to you what I did.  So
what are we doing first?  We are
extracting the names of all the output classes from the model that we have loaded here.
Our output classes are high,
medium, low.  We stored that in class labels.
Ok?  Now
what are we doing inside the Predict output?
Creating the data frame again.  Then we are
doing the same work.  We are bringing out the predicted class.
Here you will get high, low or medium as
answer.  The main change
is here.  Here you are getting probabilities.
Against all the three classes.  What is the
chance of high, what is the chance of low,
what is the chance of medium?  And then we are
converting it into a proper dictionary.
And at the end we are telling everything in return
what is the predicted category
?  What is the confidence of the predicted category
?  And what is the
probability class confidence score of all the other classes.
Ok?  So we are making these changes.
Ok?  Now let me show you
what difference will happen if you hit your API again after making these changes.
So this is the predict premium.  Let's
go try it out once.  Age 31 91
1.72 Income 10 City Mumbai.  Now if I
click on execute.  Look, this
is my output now.  Look how rich he is.   The
predicted category is coming here.
Confidence is coming at 39, high at 36, low at
39 maximum and medium at 25.  So now instead of
giving just a single answer to our user, we are
giving him a lot more information
which he can use as per his convenience.
Ok?  So I hope you understood
what changes we made.  So now we
just made this particular improvement by
adding confidence score to our API.  And this is a good practice.  If you
ever look at
machine learning API of any other company in future, you will
see that generally
along with the output, you are also told the confidence score.  The
last improvement I have planned is to
add a response model to our API.  Now you will ask
what is response model?  So till now,
if you have noticed, in all the
APIs that we have built in Fast API, we have
always
validated the data coming from the user as an in-client using a pydantic model,
right, if you look at our code, then you would see
that we have created this entire pydantic model
only for the
data that we are getting from the user.  We should be able to validate it
and then use it after validating it.
In Toast API you always
validate the input data with
the help of Pydentic.  Buttest API
also gives you the option to validate the
data being output from your API if you wish.
Again using
pydantic and it is useful in many scenarios.
For example, if you take our example,
our first output was very simple.
We were outputting a string by simply saying high, medium, low.
But now
look, after giving the confidence score,
our return, which is our output
of the API, is a very complex structure.
Right?  So what you can do in such a situation is
that you
can also validate what is going into the output with the
help of a pedantic model and to implement this whole thing
we use the concept of response model.
What exactly is a response model?  It is written here
In First API a response model
defines the structure of the data that your
API endpoint will return.   The
benefit of adding this is that your
API docs will become cleaner.  There you will be
told in advance what kind of
output you can expect.  You
can validate the output.  If the correct response is
not coming from the API, an error will be raised
and any unnecessary data will
also be filtered out from the response.  Ok
?  So that is why it is always recommended
that if you are returning even a little bit complex output
through your API then you should
use a response model.
To validate it.  Ok?  So first thing
we'll do is we'll create a Pydantic
model to validate our output.
So for that I will go to
schema and I will create a new file.  A
let's call this new file prediction
underscore response
dotpy.  Now inside this you have to create a pydantic
model.  I'm not writing all that code by hand.
I have already written it.
I will paste it directly.   Let
me guide you
what I did here.  I have created a new class
called PredictionResponse.  Now look in this,
we have added three fields.  One is the
predicted category.  You
can compare it carefully here.  Ok?
First is the predicted category.  Sorry this is
predicted category.  followed by
confidence and then class
probabilities.  Ok?  These are the three things we are
returning.  Now inside that also, if
you pay attention, we are telling things that the
predicted category will be a string.   The
confidence score will be a float and the class
probabilities will be a dictionary
where the keys will be strings but the
values ​​will be floats.  Ok?  Apart from this
we have made all three required.  A
description has been added in all three and
examples have also been given in all three, like this.
Ok?  So, this is our
prediction response model. Now
what we will do is we will come to our appy and here
we will write from schema dot
prediction
response import prediction response. Okay
and now you don't have to do anything else, you simply have to
come to your endpoint and
write the response model here and the name of the model
is prediction response.  What will happen now?
Here automatically when you send the output
to the client, it will first be
validated through this Spidertic model.  If things are
validated correctly then only you will
see the result in the output.  Ok?  Let
me try this whole
thing out once.  So now the interesting thing to see is
that if you go to the docs, nothing has
changed here but here if you look in schemas,
you have a schema called prediction response,
which you
can expand and see that predicted category will be visible,
there we have given the description, given the
example, confidence will be visible, given the
description, given the example,
class probabilities will be visible and
we have shown the example of that also here, so
whichever client it is, by seeing this particular thing, he will
understand that
in what format the data will be returned to him from this API.  Ok
?  Here you also have the input one.
You can see this also easily.  Ok?
What do you have to do?  I have to go here again.
Write out
1.72 10 LPA Mumbai and you are getting your
response.
Ok?
Here we can write the response instead of the predicted category.
Ok?  So that here, when we
click on execute again, let's say, then
we should see the response here and
within the response, our complete response will come in this format.
Ok?  So guys, this is our
last improvement.  Now if you turn around and
look at your entire API, this is a
proper industry grade API application.
Where we
improved things to the extent possible.
Separation of concerns has been put in place and
basically the entire API has been developed in a very good manner.
Now
what our goal will be in the next video is that we will Dockerize this entire API
application and then
in the next video, we will deploy that Dockerized
container, that Dockerized application
on AWS.  Ok?  So
I hope you found today's video meaningful.
First of all, you should not feel
that why did we do all this work in vain.  You
could have dockerized and deployed it directly.  I really hope I was
able to explain to you why it is important to do all this.
Ok?  So if you
liked this video please like it.  If
you have not subscribed to this channel,
please do subscribe.  See you
in the next video.  Bye.